<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<software-distribution project="MinGW" home="http://mingw.org" issue="2012073100">

  <!-- File: msys-cygutils.xml -->

  <package-collection subsystem="msys">
    <download-host uri="http://prdownloads.sourceforge.net/mingw/%F?download" />
    <package name="msys-cygutils">
      <description lang="en" title="A collection of simple utilities" >
        <paragraph>The cygutils package contains a collection of simple
          utilities from various sources. It provides mkshortcut and
          readshortcut, for creating and reading windows-style shortcuts.
          It provides getclip and putclip, for copying between stdin/stdout
          and the Windows clipboard. It also provides lpr-basic.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>A note about lpr-basic: lpr-basic spools a file to the
          specified printer device. MSYS provides two separate
          implementations: lpr-basic.exe and lpr-enhanced (the latter is a
          script, not a binary executable, and is available in the
          msys-lpr-enhanced package). lpr-basic.exe is suitable for most
          simple printing needs; it can send "raw" data to any installed
          Windows printer. This is most useful for raw text, for sending
          plain PostScript files to PostScript-compatible printers, and for
          re-sending .prn files generated using Windows' own print-to-file
          capabilities to the specific printer for which the .prn file was
          generated. For more information, see `man lpr-basic'. On the other
          hand, lpr-enhanced is an MSYS extension which supports many of the
          advanced capabilities of a true Unix-style lpr implementation.
          However, it is more difficult to configure. See the documentation
          embedded within the lpr-enhanced script for more information.
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>The msys-cygutils package provides many of the utilities
          included in the cygutils distribution. Note that the 'dos2unix'
          utilities are NOT provided by this package; the separate msys-dos2unix
          package provides versions of those utilities derived from alternate
          sources.
        </paragraph>
      </description>

      <source tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-src.tar.%" />
      <licence tarname="cygutils-%-msys-%-lic.tar.%" />

      <component class="bin">
        <requires eq="msys-core-*-msys-*-bin.tar" />
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-bin.tar.lzma">
          <requires eq="msys-libpopt-*-msys-*-dll-0.tar" />
        </release>
      </component>

      <component class="doc">
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-doc.tar.lzma" />
      </component>

      <component class="lic">
        <release tarname="cygutils-1.3.4-4-msys-1.0.13-lic.tar.lzma" />
      </component>
    </package>

  </package-collection>
</software-distribution>
<!-- vim: set nocompatible expandtab fileformat=unix textwidth=80 tabstop=2 shiftwidth=2: -->
